this tutorial is about em phones in
本教程是关于em手机的
本质冲动
this tutorial is about em phones in
essence impulse
这是v形折叠，而将标签粘在
v4到页面，然后有其他默认值
essence impulse
it's a v-fold and the tabs that glue the
这个设计基于
覆盖的锐角V字体
it's a v-fold and the tabs that glue the
v4 to the page then have other defaults
在本教程的基础上
一种非对称V字体，包含在
v4 to the page then have other defaults
glued into them this design is based on
教程4，所以这是不对称的
V折然后有酮
glued into them this design is based on
an acute angle V font which is covered
内置于沟渠中的V型折叠
区别在于与众不同
an acute angle V font which is covered
in tutorial to this one this is based on
不对称和另一个对称
在这种情况下，所有标签都位于
in tutorial to this one this is based on
a asymmetric V font which is covered in
在这个模型中，只有两个标签
在模型前面出现
a asymmetric V font which is covered in
tutorial 4 and so here is the asymmetric
而这只是设计问题
从机械上来说，不管你是哪个
tutorial 4 and so here is the asymmetric
V fold and then it just has a ketone
在此示例中这样做只是向您显示
你可以开始做什么，你可以转向
V fold and then it just has a ketone
v-folds built into the gullies the
您可以通过折叠产生一个整体
系列飞机有六架飞机，但是
v-folds built into the gullies the
difference is the apart from one being
还有各种各样的沟渠
好，您可以添加计数器的沟渠
difference is the apart from one being
asymmetric and the other symmetric in
像这样折叠给他们，你可以
切柠檬然后推碎
asymmetric and the other symmetric in
this case all the tabs are behind in the
你可以用那些山折
沟壑创造更多
this case all the tabs are behind in the
model in this one there's just two tabs
然后可以玩的飞机
这是这只鸟的
model in this one there's just two tabs
which come forward in front of the model
n折只是一个
简单的电话
which come forward in front of the model
and it's all just a question of design
粘住它的标签已经放好了
在它后面，这样他们就不会弄乱
and it's all just a question of design
mechanically it doesn't matter which you
设计这是一个EM折叠
曾经举起另一架飞机，所以这是
mechanically it doesn't matter which you
do in this example this just shows you
实际上是平行折叠，是弯曲的
折叠所有的云都做成一个结局
do in this example this just shows you
what you can start doing you can turn
折叠，所以我们拿一张底纸
把它弄好一半，然后把一半
what you can start doing you can turn
thee the em fold generates a whole
折叠成两半
将它折成两半
thee the em fold generates a whole
series of planes there's six planes but
而我们在这里所做的是
我们在教程中看到的基本V折
series of planes there's six planes but
there's also a whole array of gullies as
2，但不同之处在于
刚开始在底角附近
there's also a whole array of gullies as
well and the gullies you can add counter
并制作两个小的粘合标签
将开始约​​三分之一的方式
well and the gullies you can add counter
folds to them like this you can you can
所以这是第一个折痕开始
大约三分之一
folds to them like this you can you can
cut lemons and push pieces through so
向外折痕
边缘，什么都没关系
cut lemons and push pieces through so
you can use those mountain folds and
角度，你做不同的角度会
给你不同的形状，所以如果你想
you can use those mountain folds and
gullies to create a whole lot of more
想玩一个特定的形状
围绕它直到找到角度
gullies to create a whole lot of more
planes that you can then play around
你在这里所以打开它
折痕全部下降
planes that you can then play around
with this is this bird's this is made
指向箭头那里有折痕
现在将它对折，然后切一个楔子
with this is this bird's this is made
with an n-fold it's just a
所有折痕相遇的地方
之后楔入，所以现在您有了这个
with an n-fold it's just a
straightforward n phone
形状，所以现在只需向上折叠一面
你要增加另一个折痕
straightforward n phone
the tabs that glue it down have been put
这是您的首折，现在
这样上来绝不能从这里开始
the tabs that glue it down have been put
behind it so they don't mess up the
在这一点上，它必须在某个地方
沿着这个折线，所以说三分之一
behind it so they don't mess up the
design this one this is an EM fold being
的方式，然后将其折叠
必须倾斜，所以这是你的
design this one this is an EM fold being
used to raise another plane so this is
首先是这种脊椎
然后
used to raise another plane so this is
actually a parallel fold it's a curved
如果倾斜的话要倾斜
这样就无法工作，然后折叠
actually a parallel fold it's a curved
fold all the clouds are made with an end
回到自己那是现在的一侧
我们将另一面折叠起来
fold all the clouds are made with an end
fold so we take a base sheet fold it in
不必与您相同的角度
只要
fold so we take a base sheet fold it in
half crease it well and take half a
折角倾斜远离
中心折叠数据
half crease it well and take half a
sheet and fold it in half so just fold
很好地将其折叠起来
现在将其全部打开，在这里
sheet and fold it in half so just fold
it in half crease it really thoroughly
现在您开始演奏六角琴，所以从
中间折成山折
it in half crease it really thoroughly
and what what we're making here is is a
下一折将是山谷
下一个山下一个
and what what we're making here is is a
basic V fold as we looked at in tutorial
一个山谷，所以你可以六角琴和
另一端以
basic V fold as we looked at in tutorial
2 but with the difference that instead
中间的山褶
山谷下一个山
2 but with the difference that instead
of just starting near the bottom corner
一辆面包车，您现在可以很好地捏住
现在可以打开它
of just starting near the bottom corner
and making two small gluing tabs we're
坚持这样的事情
必须把这个中央折痕排好
and making two small gluing tabs we're
going to start about a third of the way
与中央沟整个事情
当它关闭时，它将向前折叠
going to start about a third of the way
up so this is the first crease start
所以你想要的那一边
页面，您可以在
up so this is the first crease start
about a third of the way up and you have
返回，如果你想取决于你
设计，也可以在附近
about a third of the way up and you have
a crease coming up towards the outer
前面你也可以很紧
所以你有一个非常狭窄的山脊
a crease coming up towards the outer
edges and it doesn't really matter what
中间也可以宽一点
你走得越多，它就会躺下，然后
edges and it doesn't really matter what
angle you do the different angles will
这些是与山褶皱
他们后面可以玩的沟壑
angle you do the different angles will
give you different shapes so if you want
因此，我们可能会尝试
在我们坚持之前
give you different shapes so if you want
to want to a specific shape just play
所以他们拿第一名，我们就转
把它放到柜台电话里，以便我们折叠
to want to a specific shape just play
around with it till you find the angle
然后将其推回现在
我们又产生了两架飞机
around with it till you find the angle
that you were so here it is open it up
将能够与我们一起玩
接下来的两个相同，我们可以
that you were so here it is open it up
the creases all make a big downward
将它们折叠起来，你必须这样做
在你坚持下去之前，有很多
the creases all make a big downward
pointing arrow there's the creases there
更容易，所以我们在那里
我还有两架飞机，我们可以做
pointing arrow there's the creases there
now fold it in half and just cut a wedge
同样在这里，你可以做这些褶皱
无论从哪个角度来看都没关系
now fold it in half and just cut a wedge
where all the creases meet just cut a
这全都取决于什么
塑造你想要的
where all the creases meet just cut a
wedge after that so now you have this
幸运的是我们可以离开
在那，现在把它粘在你身上
wedge after that so now you have this
shape so now just fold up one side and
首先你要决定什么
你想要的角度你有多紧
shape so now just fold up one side and
you're going to add another crease so
想要它站起来你想要多少
躺着我要去找东西
you're going to add another crease so
here's your initial fold now you're
这样，所以前两个折痕
到脊椎大约45度
here's your initial fold now you're
coming up like this mustn't start here
然后把胶水涂在一侧
像这样粘下来就可以了
coming up like this mustn't start here
at this point it's got to be somewhere
它关闭把胶水粘在另一个
然后您跟随Shutts折叠
at this point it's got to be somewhere
along this fold line so say a third of
整个基础射击，使其自然
粘住位置确实用力按
along this fold line so say a third of
the way and then fold it up this fold it
确保你儿子的胶水打开
它有，我刚刚有你的M折
the way and then fold it up this fold it
has to be leaning away so here's your
列举了一些商业案例
书，所以这是野生海盗的地方
has to be leaning away so here's your
first of all this sort of spine one and
去航行，如果你看到的话
这是主要的V形折叠
first of all this sort of spine one and
then
这里的小计数器形式是M
折叠，它有更多的触角
then
to be leaning away if it leans in with
粘在那些上，在这种情况下
外位片被用作
to be leaning away if it leans in with
that way it won't work and then fold
肌肉提起较大的较大部分
卡这实际上不是
that way it won't work and then fold
that back on itself that's one side now
n折，这些都是多余的小块
卡在里面，他们朝外
that back on itself that's one side now
we'll do the other side fold it up it
玫瑰在这M折
角度指向这一点是一个M
we'll do the other side fold it up it
doesn't have to be the same angle you
字体，所以这是主要的B
在这里折叠，然后在V形折叠
doesn't have to be the same angle you
can play around with it as long as the
一方面，在这边
另一个V但有一个额外的
can play around with it as long as the
angle of the fold is leaning away from
卡在下一张卡上的是
基思的非自然历史博物馆
angle of the fold is leaning away from
the center fold data
Mobic，这里我们有一个整体
阵列这是一个完整的M折系列
the center fold data
crease it well fold it back on its own
给你
蜘蛛的腿，我认为
crease it well fold it back on its own
right now open it all flat so here it is
快要结束了，另一个
在这里计算出它的结构
right now open it all flat so here it is
now you concertina it so start with the
所有的东西都是n折的，所以你有
肩膀的主体
now you concertina it so start with the
middle fold that into a mountain fold
原始的v-phone，您有一个
EM折叠在这里，抬起您已经抬起的手臂
middle fold that into a mountain fold
the next fold is going to be a valley
在这里得到另一个折痕
这只手臂，它有一系列的
the next fold is going to be a valley
and the next one a mountain the next one
复杂的点点滴滴，这是一个
弯曲的形状，这是所有的平行折叠
and the next one a mountain the next one
a valley so you can concertina and the
提起其他零碎的东西
这个设计，所以下一个是
a valley so you can concertina and the
same on the other side starting with the
《尼克胡桃夹子》中的胡桃夹子
在这个非凡的传播
same on the other side starting with the
mountain fold in the middle next one's a
回来，你有它的主体是
M折，然后这是一个盒子
mountain fold in the middle next one's a
valley next one's a mountain next one's
返回这是教程14这是一个
浮动飞机在这里，这是教程12
valley next one's a mountain next one's
a van you just pinch it all well now you
但是大部分是这个
主V折在中间，然后
a van you just pinch it all well now you
can open it up now this is going to
你有这些展开的翅膀
每边，最后一个是爱丽丝
can open it up now this is going to
stick down something like this you've
仙境与造纸工程
安迪·曼斯菲尔德（Andy Mansfield），准备好这一件事是
stick down something like this you've
got to have this central crease lined up
打开时真的很大声
嘿
got to have this central crease lined up
with the central gully the whole thing
最后所有的M折
变化和品种正在解释
with the central gully the whole thing
as it closes it's going to fold forward
这是我的纸上弹出书设计
机械师
as it closes it's going to fold forward
so the side where you want it on the
您